restek.com 2018-09-27

# Privacy Policy / Restek.com

Effective: 13 January 2015

Restek Corporation and its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively "Restek") are committed to the protection of their customers' privacy and the security of any personal information provided to Restek. 

The websites [www.restek.com](http://www.restek.com/) and [blog.restek.com](http://blog.restek.com/) ("our websites") are owned and operated by Restek (referred to herein as "we," "us," or "our"). The purpose of our privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") is to inform you about the types of personally identifiable information we gather about you when you visit our websites, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. The phrases "personally identifiable information" or "personal information" mean any information by which you can be identified, such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, etc. This Privacy Policy applies only to users accessing our websites from the United States. Please read our complete Privacy Policy. By using our websites, you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this website, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy, please do not use this website.

This website may use "cookies." A "cookie" is a small file stored by your web browser to help a particular system, like ours, recognize you and the pages you visit on our websites. We built our websites to offer numerous conveniences and useful functions—such as the shopping cart and forms that prefill—and we rely on cookies to make such things possible. The information we store in and access from cookies is not sold to vendors, advertisers, direct mail concerns, e-mail list services, etc. If you disable cookies, certain functions of the website may not work properly or be available to you. Users of our websites may also receive cookies from certain third-party sites that provide services to Restek and help us improve our ability to reach and serve our customers online. None of the cookies encountered at our websites contain personally identifiable or privileged information. We do employ Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting, which provides us with certain aggregate and non-personally identifiable information such as age, gender, and interests; however, as stated above, we do not share cookie data with any third parties, nor do we combine the personally identifiable information you voluntarily submit to us with the non-personally identifiable information we collect through Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Those who wish to opt out of this third-party demographics and interest reporting can do so via Google's ads settings or the Network Advertising Initiative's consumer opt-out.

The only personally identifiable information that is collected by Restek is that which is expressly volunteered by users. We hold this information confidential and take appropriate technical and policy measures to protect it. Our use of such data is strictly internal; it is not sold and it is not shared with companies outside of the Restek's distribution network. We strive to make our websites useful and relevant for our customers through ongoing improvement, which depends on understanding how people use them and how they arrived (i.e., referring pages). Restek makes no attempt to monitor or track visitors' activities on any other sites. We do not change our information-collection practices or use of cookies based on the do not track settings in your browser.

Our websites may contain links to other websites. We have no control over the privacy practices or the content of any of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors, or other sites to which we provide links from our websites. Restek does not endorse, approve, or certify these other websites, and we do not guarantee the accuracy, completeness, efficacy, or timeliness of the information contained on these sites. This Privacy Policy applies to information collected by our websites, and you should check the applicable privacy policy of the website operator when visiting other websites.

Restek will take reasonable steps to protect your personally identifiable information that you transmit to us and to protect such information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet transmission or data storage is ever fully secure, and Restek cannot guarantee that information transmitted via our websites or stored by us will remain confidential at all times. When we collect other information from our website users, it is stored in an area to which the general public does not have access. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to ensure that personal information is stored and treated responsibly.

Please bear in mind that, to the extent you are provided with access credentials to access portions of our websites, anyone you provide with your access credentials will also have access to your account and, possibly, to your personally identifiable information. If you use our websites, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your access credentials and for restricting access to your computer. 

Restek is the sole owner of all information collected on our websites. In addition, as we develop our business, we may sell our business or buy another business. In such transactions, customer information is generally one of the transferred business assets. In the event that Restek or substantially all of its assets are acquired, personal information about our customers may be one of the transferred assets.

Restek will disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on Restek; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Restek; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of our websites or the public.

If you provide your e-mail address to us, you may receive e-mail from us relating to new products and services or upcoming events. Also, technical assistance may be provided via e-mail, and we may send surveys and questionnaires that help us offer better products and services in the future. You can request that we do not send e-mail to you via the links below. 

If you supply us with your telephone number, you may receive telephone contact from us for order confirmation or technical assistance. Also, you may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. You can request that we do not call you.

If you supply us with your postal address, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. Also, you may receive mailings from our corporate partners. You can instruct us not to send you mail. 

Restek Corporation respects your privacy. Upon your request we will refrain from contacting you. Use the links below, or contact us by telephone, fax, or mail.

Restek reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a new version thereof on our websites. Please check this page periodically for changes. When changes are made we will update the effective date of this Policy. (See [top of page](http://www.restek.com/Privacy-Policy#top).) 

  * [**Subscribe**](http://www.restek.com/subscribe)to receive Restek technical publications via e-mail. 
  * [**Unsubscribe**](http://www.restek.com/unsubscribe) to remove your e-mail address from our list. 
  * [**Contact Restek Web Support**](http://www.restek.com/webhelp) with any other instructions regarding communication from Restek.
